<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>customization on beytan.net</title><link>https://www.beytan.net/categories/customization/</link><description>Recent content in customization on beytan.net</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>tr-tr</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 15:23:50 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.beytan.net/categories/customization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Delete Additional Keyboard on Windows10</title><link>https://www.beytan.net/posts/customization/delete-additional-keyboard-on-windows10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 15:23:50 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.beytan.net/posts/customization/delete-additional-keyboard-on-windows10/</guid><description>Why the need? Why the Keyboard Layout Anyone with a non-english country probably has one or more languages and probably their respective keyboard layouts available to them.
In Turkey, we have a Turkish-Q keyboard layout and our keyboards are mostly in this layout as hardware.
Here is a quick glance of how it is, thanks to Microsoft: https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/globalization/keyboards/kbdtuq.html
What has changed in Windows10 You used to delete this additional keyboard layout so that it just doesn&amp;rsquo;t switch from one to the other during your usage.</description></item><item><title>Desktop Pc Setup</title><link>https://www.beytan.net/posts/customization/desktop-pc-setup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 21:10:32 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.beytan.net/posts/customization/desktop-pc-setup/</guid><description>Tools to install: Avira Antivir AutoHotKey 7Zip 1Password Ditto Google Drive Dropbox VSCode Spotify Winamp Discord Git Firefox Chrome Greenshot (Screenshot tool) Notion GameManagers (Steam, Origin, AmazonGames, Epic, UPlay) GameSaveManager (To restore local saved games) Some media player (Potplayer, VLC, should decide) Torrent tool (qBittorrent, should decide) Slack WinDirStat Restic Backup VPN (Surfshark, NordVPN) Drivers, runtimes to install: NVidia GeForce Java runtime Razr keyboard, mouse drivers Steelseries arctis 7 driver Steps before re-installing Windows Manually trigger last restic backup Sync Drives (Firefox account, Google Drive, Dropbox) Manually copy media folders to a backup location /Users/&amp;lt;user&amp;gt;Documents /Users/&amp;lt;user&amp;gt;Pictures /Users/&amp;lt;user&amp;gt;Desktop /Users/&amp;lt;user&amp;gt;Downloads Manually take screenshots of Dota Settings screens Backup saved games through GameSave-Manager Backup Steam games to a Library folder on another disk if it&amp;rsquo;s in C: Push git folders Prepare Windows installation USB using Installation Media Creation Tool</description></item></channel></rss>